出来了
来把眼罩戴上
带好了
平躺到床上呈大字形
对就这样真乖
主人把你的四肢绑到床上去
喂张开嘴
张大主人把这个东西塞进去
嘴张大含住了
那么主人
就
说了
小美啊
你终于来了
让你看看你未婚夫的真面目
对呀
他就是一条贱狗s狗屁的s
你看一点都没有羞耻心
给你翻的消费记录
他最近还找过女孩子调教呢
哼上次我去你家就已经把他识破了
小美别哭了
先别走
等我穿上衣服
我们走吧
就让他绑在这里吧
咱们也别锁门
等明天早上让酒店服务员给他解绑
小美回到这里之后
我就想赶紧联系到你
一开始我以为你只是和他交往
没想到那么快
你们明年就要结婚了
所以我一定要来看看他对你好不好
谁知道他结果
不说这个了
小美我好想你啊
我好想念以前的时候啊
以前怎么在寝室住的时候
你睡在我上铺
直到有一次我半夜起来喝水
这才发现你的秘密
你还记得吗
你的第一个项圈是我给你买的
后来我要考研
就忽略了对你的关心
没时间陪你玩了
你就找到了别的主人
后来你就遇到了你的先生
你也就喜欢上了他
好了不提他
我们不提他
其实一开始我也以为咱们只是在sm少互相依靠对方
可是分开之后
我发现我不只是喜欢你的身体
你也是这样吗
tell me that you want me
哼不是喜欢我神秘的情绪而来
想念姐姐对你的控制吗
almost here and there
想让姐姐好好爱你吗
来叫声好听的
嗯
只叫姐姐可不行
有救
主人
真乖想到那些男人哪懂你的好啊
还是主人更懂你
you're only we know
only
we know about us
all about us
scare you
windo
about us
all about us
all about
oh baby
i remember back in lights of tember
因为我just free in the night
oh i see
we drove to fit
yet
the night with you was enlika
no
no peace
you always on my mind
waiting for the sun
cross every night
i'll rush feeling
sorry
putting on the shark
keep it on the low
but i do resit goes
but i wanna take it slowly
it's a little secret
tell me
can you keep it
i know that i can't get
啦啦啦啦
and if you want to  down
only
we know
and only we know
only
we know about us
all about us
scare you weird
only
we know
only we know
only
we know about us on the balloon
the bus
when we know
and when you we know
and we know got us
all about us
now
you're the willow
we know
i wanna know
we know about us
all about us
all about su
i don't wanna lie
yeah
i give it all sukit
all sugi
don't wanna lie
yeah
the sun
you ball su